American Expeditionary Forces
Marist College
American Expeditionary Forces
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.3
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - American Expeditionary Forces, 2.1.1.2.3
              - Margaret Wilson with American soldiers, circa 1918; 35 (Box 1320)
                3.5x5
              - Margaret Wilson with American soldier, circa 1918; 36
              - Captain Donald Stone, circa 1918; 37
              - Cathedral of Tours, circa 1918; 38
                3.5x4.5
              - Cathedral of Tours, circa 1918; 39
              - Street lined with buildings, people lining the sidewalk, circa 1918; 40
              - Soldier and woman in front of office building, circa 1918; 41
              - Two soldiers standing outside café, circa 1918; 42
                3.5x4.75
              - Two men pulling cart in street, automobile in background, circa 1918; 43
              - Soldier sleeping on bench next to four women, circa 1918; 44
              - Soldiers sitting outside the Y.M.C.A “Eagle Hut”, circa 1918; 45
              - Two soldiers and woman standing amongst trees in front of building, circa 1918; 46
                4x5
              - Soldier holding child dressed as sailor, child’s hat says “U.S.S. Long Beach”, circa 1918; 47
                3.5x4x5
              - Soldier with cane standing on sidewalk with elaborate building in background, circa 1918; 48
              - Soldiers sitting in horse buggy with another buggy full of soldiers behind, circa 1918; 49
              - Lowell Thomas tickling woman, soldier and old woman looking on, circa 1918; 50
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in Paris talking to two soldiers, circa 1918; 51
              - Lowell Thomas, operating motion picture camera, records soldier kissing a woman, circa 1918; 52
              - Two soldiers talking to a woman, Lowell Thomas operating motion picture camera, circa 1918; 53
              - Two soldiers and two women in front of an elaborate building, circa 1918; 54
              - Garden of an elaborate building, circa 1918; 55
              - Two soldiers and two women in front of elaborate building, circa 1918; 56
              - Soldiers and women in front of elaborate building, circa 1918; 57
              - Two soldiers talking to children, circa 1918; 58
              - Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi talking to soldiers at outdoor café, circa 1918; 59
                2.5x3.25
                film
              - Woman attempting to give soldier a flower in pot, circa 1918; 60
                2x3
              - Soldier talking to woman with basket, circa 1918; 1 (Box 1321)
              - Soldiers and civilians standing in street, circa 1918; 2
              - Soldiers standing on sidewalk, children in the street, circa 1918; 3
              - Two soldiers standing outside building with women and children, circa 1918; 4
              - Aerial view of city and ships by docks, blimp flying in distance, circa 1918; 5
              - Tree lined street, people walking down street next to river, circa 1918; 6
              - Many soldiers overlooking small town, circa 1918; 7
              - Aerial view of country road and river lined with houses and trees, circa 1918; 8
              - Soldier standing among rocks [ruins?] overlooking house and fields, circa 1918; 9
              - Soldier looking over fields, houses from a hill, circa 1918; 10
              - Two soldiers pointing up a hill at soldiers standing on ruins, circa 1918; 11
              - Automobile driving on street lined with trees, circa 1918; 12
              - Group of soldiers sitting in field, hills in background, circa 1918; 13
                2.5x3.5
              - Group of soldiers in field, military equipment in foreground, circa 1918; 14
              - Soldiers standing in front of statue, more soldiers in background, circa 1918; 15
              - Spectators watching soldiers in ceremony, circa 1918; 16
              - Soldiers marching through street, large crowd of spectators watching, circa 1918; 17
              - Soldiers marching through street, spectators watching from sidewalk, circa 1918; 18
              - Soldiers filling street in distance, spectators lining the sidewalk, circa 1918; 19
              - Soldiers marching down street, children running alongside the soldiers, circa 1918; 20
              - Soldiers marching down street, close-up, child marching next to soldiers, circa 1918; 21
              - Soldiers marching in street, women and children watching, circa 1918; 22
                3.5x4.6
              - Close-up of American military wagon, circa 1918; 23
              - Soldiers and nuns standing together in doorway, circa 1918; 24
              - Two soldiers, one holding two guns, one holding a gas mask, circa 1918; 25
              - Soldiers on ship, circa 1918; 26
              - Soldiers on ship looking at camera, circa 1918; 27
              - Soldiers on ship, circa 1918; 28
              - Soldiers in automobile driving through town street, circa 1918; 29
              - Soldiers sitting outside at table, eating, automobile in background, circa 1918; 30
              - Soldiers helping two women fill baskets, house in background, circa 1918; 31
              - Soldiers in line, going into kitchen at base, circa 1918; 32
              - Overhead view of city and boats at docks, circa 1918; 33
              - Ship in harbor, tree branches on bottom and left, circa 1918; 34
              - Soldiers sitting on large machine, circa 1918; 35
              - Troops marching past military buildings [?], circa 1918; 36
              - Three soldiers in front of house in wooded area, circa 1918; 37
              - Soldiers standing outside building surrounded by trees, circa 1918; 38
              - Four military men looking at camera as soldiers on horseback walk past, circa 1918; 39
              - Seven military men standing on deck of ship, circa 1918; 40
              - Soldiers examining crashed airplane in field, circa 1918; 41
              - Truck full of soldiers in a town, circa 1918; 42
              - Two tanks angled out of trenches toward sky, circa 1918; 43
              - Airplane just off ground, other airplanes on either side, circa 1918; 44
              - Family and dog looking at airplane, two cows in front of airplane, circa 1918; 45
              - Pilot sitting in airplane next to plane hanger, circa 1918; 46
              - Pilots congregated in front of line of airplanes, man operating motion picture camera, circa 1918; 47
              - Two men sitting in airplane, circa 1918; 48
              - Workers standing nearby airplane, circa 1918; 49
              - Men surveying front propeller on airplane, circa 1918; 50
              - Workers standing next to propeller of airplane, pilot sitting on airplane, circa 1918; 51
              - Airplane in cloud covered sky, circa 1918; 52
              - Airplane flying in cloud covered sky, circa 1918; 53
              - Soldiers standing in front of destroyed house looking at a box, circa 1918; 54
              - Man standing in doorway of building, buildings on either side destroyed, circa 1918; 55
              - Brick building, half destroyed, circa 1918; 56
              - Unidentified structure in ruins, circa 1918; 57
              - Unidentified structure in ruins, circa 1918; 58
              - Two standing buildings among ruins, circa 1918; 59
              - Building lined streets, many buildings in ruins, sidewalk filled with ruins, circa 1918; 60
              - Half-destroyed buildings, street in foreground, circa 1918; 61
              - Two automobiles on street next to half destroyed house, ruins in foreground, circa 1918; 62
              - Men surveying ruins of large building, circa 1918; 63
              - Man standing in ruins, looking into the remaining part of building, circa 1918; 64
              - Street lined with ruined buildings, column falling in center, circa 1918; 65
              - Man pointing to a wall partly in ruins, circa 1918; 66
              - Group of men standing in ruins, looking at camera, circa 1918; 67
              - Officers with pistols climbing through the ruins of a building, wires hanging from above, circa 1918; 68
              - Officers pointing pistols at another soldier amid ruins, circa 1918; 69
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins, circa 1918; 70
                1.5x3
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins talking to two other men, circa 1918; 71
                2.25x3.5
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins with two others, looking at camera, circa 1918; 72
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing amid ruins looking to side, circa 1918; 73
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Harry G. Thomas, and Major Piero Tozzi standing in front of ruined house, circa 1918; 74
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of farmhouse, circa 1918; 75
              - House in ruins, circa 1918; 76
              - Soldiers on the S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 77
              - Soldiers on S.S. Leviathon watching boat, circa 1918; 78
              - Machinery and soldiers on deck of S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 79
              - Soldier standing against machinery on deck of S.S. Leviathon, circa 1918; 80
              - Soldier using lasso on S.S. Leviathon, other soldiers looking on, circa 1918; 81
              - Soldiers sitting on decks of S.S. Leviathon next to life boats, circa 1918; 82
              - Place Stanislas, Lorraine, circa 1918; 83
              - Statue of George Washington, Paris, circa 1918; 84
                5x7
              - Lowell Thomas at a monument for Waldeck Rousseau, reflection, Paris, circa 1918; 85
              - Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in automobile outside the Hotel Regina, motion picture camera on front of car, Paris, circa 1918; 86
              - Lowell Thomas with motion picture camera, and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas in automobile outside the Hotel Regina, Paris, circa 1918; 87
              - Man and woman in horse drawn cart, circa 1918; 88
                3x5
              - Two women, man, and child in horse drawn carriage in front of ruins, circa 1918; 89
              - Two men, two women, and child in horse drawn cart in front of ruins, circa 1918; 90
              - View of church spires from window, Paris, 1917; 1 (Box 1322)
              - Street scene, cathedral in distance, Paris, 1917; 2
              - Street scene, tower in distance, 1917; 3
              - Large fountain in front of ornate building, man sitting on ground in front of fountain, 1917; 4
              - Crowd of people and automobile in front of the Hotel Cailleux, 1917; 5
              - Le Matin, Paris, 1917; 6
              - Five men, standing next to automobile, reading map, 1917; 7
              - Ornate room, France [?], 1917; 8